Inventory of the Jay Kennedy video tapes collection
Hoover Institution Archives
Jay Kennedy video tapes collection
1970-1974
80202
Kennedy, Jay, collector.
3 cubic foot boxes (3 linear feet)
Hoover Institution Archives Stanford, California 94305-6010
Videotape cassettes of television broadcasts of speeches and remarks by Ronald Reagan as governor of California, relating to California state politics.
Administrative Information
Access
The collection is open for research
Access to audiovisual materials requires at least two weeks advance notice. Audiovisual materials include sound recordings, video recordings, and motion picture film. Hoover staff will determine whether use copies of the materials requested can be made available. Some materials may not be accessible even with advance notice. Please contact the Hoover Institution Archives Audiovisual Specialist for further information.
Acquisition Information
Materials were acquired by the Hoover Institution Archives in 1980
Accruals
Materials may have been added to the collection since this finding aid was prepared. To determine if this has occurred, find the collection in Stanford University's online catalog Socrates at http://library.stanford.edu/webcat. Materials have been added to the collection if the number of boxes listed in Socrates is larger than the number of boxes listed in this finding aid.
Biography Note
Scope and Content of Collection
Videotape cassettes of television broadcasts of speeches and remarks by Ronald Reagan as governor of California, relating to California state politics.
Indexing Terms
The following terms have been used to index the description of this collection in Stanford University's online catalog.
Subjects
Reagan, Ronald; Radio broadcasting – United States; United States – Politics and government; Presidents – United States – Elections; Elections – California; California- Politics and government
Related Material
Ronald Reagan Radio Commentary: sound recordings, 1975-1979, Hoover Institution Archives
Citizens Committee to Elect Ronald Reagan Governor, 1966, Hoover Institution Archives
Ronald Reagan subject collection, 1948-2004, Hoover Institution Archives
Container List
- Unidentified, undated; Length: unknown 1 tape, Dub.
- Governors Report to the People, undated; Length: 60 1 tape, Dub.
- News Release, Dr. Parkinson Statement, ORA "Brown's Hatchet Man", undated; Length: unknown 1 tape, Dub.
- News Release, 10/19, Spencer Williams Statement "Tax-paid Campaigner", undated; Length: unknown 2 tapes, Dub.
- Governor Reagan with students, 9/25/1970; Length: unknown 1 tape, Dub.
- Reagan-Murphy :30, 9/31/1970; Length: 1:10 1 tape, Master
- Reagan-Pork :30, 9/31/1970; Length: 1:10 1 tape, Master
- Reagan-Pork :10, 9/31/1970; Length: 1:10 1 tape, Master
- Remarks by Ronald Reagan., 6/21/1973; Length: 1:15, 6 tapes, Dub.
  Includes transcript
- Statement by Governor Reagan on Signing the 3/4 Billion Dollar State Tax Rebate Bill., 8/21/1973; Length: 2:15 12 tapes, Dub.
  Includes Transcript
- News Release "Governor's Report to The People", 10/3/1973; Length: 60, 2 tapes, Dub.
- Report to The People, 2/15/1974; Length: 60 1 tape, Dub.